Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
- Medical reference files
  - Fetal life (Box 372)
  - Films (Box 372)
  - Formula (Box 372)
  - Foster children (Box 372)
  - Foundations (Box 372)
  - Freud, Sigmund (Box 372)
  - Genetics (Box 373)
  - Gifted children (Box 373)
  - Glands (Box 373)
  - Groups (Box 373)
  - Growth (Box 373)
  - Growth and development charts (Box 373)
  - Handicapped children (Box 373)
  - Harlow (Box 373)
  - Head injuries (Box 373)
  - Health and welfare (Box 373)
  - Heart disease (Box 373)
  - Hip dislocation (Box 373)
  - Hospital standards (Box 373)
  - Hospitalization (Box 373)
  - Immunization (Box 373)
  - Inborn temperament (Box 373)
  - Infant feeding (Box 373)
  - Injections (Box 373)
  - Instinct to master (Box 373)
  - Intelligence (Box 374)
  - Intelligence quotient (Box 374)
  - Integration (Box 374)
  - Intestinal obstruction (Box 374)
  - Jealousy (Box 374)
  - Kasler data (Box 374)
  - Kindergarten (Box 374)
  - Latency (Box 374)
  - Learning difficulties (Box 374)
  - Lectures (Box 374)
  - Legislation (Box 374)
  - Malformations (Box 374)
  - Marriage (Box 374)
  - Maternal deprivation (Box 374)
  - Maturity (Box 374)
  - Measles (Box 374)
  - Medical care (Box 374)
  - Medical economics (Box 374)
  - Medical education (Box 374)
  - Menstruation (Box 375)
  - Mental development (Box 375)
  - Mental health (Box 375)
  - Mental illness (Box 375)
  - Mental retardation (Box 375)
  - Metabolism (Box 375)
  - Milk (Box 375)
  - Mongolism (Box 375)
  - Mortality (Box 375)
  - Mother-child relationship (Box 375)
  - Mothers (Box 375)
  - Mumps (Box 375)
  - Muscular dystrophy (Box 375)
  - Music (Box 375)
  - Negroes (Box 375)
  - Neonatal psychology (Box 375)
  - Neonate (Box 375)
  - Neurology (Box 376)
  - Newborn (Box 376)
  - Newborn personality (Box 376)
  - Nipples (Box 376)
  - Nursery schools (Box 376)
  - Nutrition (Box 376)
  - Obesity (Box 376)
  - Obscenity (Box 376)
  - Obstetrical practice (Box 376)
  - Operations (Box 376)
  - Otitis media (Box 376)
  - Pacifiers (Box 376)
  - Pain (Box 376)
  - Parasites (Box 376)
  - Parent education (Box 376)
  - Parents (Box 376)
  - Parents Without Partners, Inc. (Box 376)
  - Parochial schools (Box 376)
  - Pediatric care (Box 377)
  - Pediatric psychiatry (Box 377)
  - Phenylketonuria (Box 377)
  - Pica (Box 377)
  - Pinworms (Box 377)
  - Pittsburgh, University of (Box 377)
  - Play (Box 377)
  - Playthings (Box 377)
  - Poison Information Center (Box 377)
  - Poisoning (Box 377)
  - Poliomyelitis (Box 377)
  - Population (Box 377)
  - Poverty (Box 377)
  - Pre-clinical training of psychiatry in medical school (Box 377)
  - Pregnancy (Box 378)
  - Prejudice (Box 378)
  - Prematurity (Box 378)
  - Prenatal development (Box 378)
  - Psychoanalysis (Box 378)
  - Psychodynamics of family life (Box 378)
  - Psychological testing (Box 378)
  - Psychology (Box 379)
  - Psychosomatic medicine (Box 379)
  - Psychotherapy (Box 379)
  - Public schools (Box 379)
  - Pyloric stenosis (Box 379)
  - Radiation (Box 379)
  - Reading (Box 379)
  - Reading disabilities (Box 379)
  - Relief (Box 379)
  - Religion (Box 379)
  - Residential treatment (Box 379)
  - Respiratory infections (Box 380)
  - Rheumatic fever (Box 380)
  - Resuscitation (Box 380)
  - Retardation (Box 380)
  - Retrolental fibroplasia (Box 380)
  - Rooming-in (Box 380)
  - Rubella (Box 380)
  - Rumination (Box 380)
  - Sabin Oral (Box 380)
  - Schizophrenia in children (Box 380)
  - School health (Box 380)
  - School phobias (Box 380)
  - Schiool underachievement (Box 380)
  - Schools, 2 folders (Box 380)
  - Schools, 2 folders (Box 381)
  - Separation (Box 381)
  - Sex education (Box 381)
  - Sexual abnormalities (Box 381)
  - Sexual attack (Box 381)
  - Siblings (Box 381)
  - Skin (Box 381)
  - Sleep (Box 381)
  - Smoking (Box 381)
  - Social work (Box 381)
  - Sociology (Box 381)
  - Speech (Box 381)
  - Staphylococcus infections (Box 381)
  - Stranger anxiety (Box 381)
  - Stridor (Box 381)
  - Stuttering (Box 381)
  - Sucking (Box 381)
  - Suffocation (Box 381)
  - Swaddling (Box 381)
  - Swimming pools (Box 381)
  - Sydenham's Chorea (Box 381)
  - Teachers (Box 381)
  - Teeth (Box 381)
  - Teeth caries (Box 381)
  - Teeth grinders (Box 381)
  - Television (Box 382)
  - Temperature (Box 382)
  - Thumb sucking (Box 382)
  - Thyroid (Box 382)
  - Toilet training (Box 382)
  - Tongue (Box 382)
  - Tonsils (Box 382)
  - Toy kit (Box 382)
  - Toys (Box 382)
  - Tranquilizers (Box 382)
  - Travel (Box 382)
  - Tuberculosis (Box 382)
  - Twins (Box 382)
  - Ulcer (Box 382)
  - Ulcerative colitis (Box 382)
  - Umbilical hernias (Box 382)
  - Undescended testicles (Box 382)
  - Upper respiratory disease (Box 382)
  - Urology (Box 382)
  - Vaccination (Box 382)
  - Vandalsim (Box 382)
  - Viruses (Box 382)
  - Vitamins (Box 382)
  - War (Box 382)
  - War Toys (Box 382)
  - Weeping (Box 382)
  - Wellesley Human Relations Service, Inc (Box 382)
  - Western Reserve University (Box 382)
  - Work (Box 382)
  - Workman's compensation (Box 382)
  - Worms (Box 382)
  - X-Rays (Box 382)
  - Youth (Box 382)
- Memorabilia
  - Address books, 5 folders / 10 volumes (Box 486)
  - Address books, 5 folders / 7 volumes (Box 487)
  - Address books, 4 folders / 7 volumes (Box 488)
  - Address books, 3 folders / 4 volumes (Box 489)
  - Address book fragments (Box 489)
  - Appointment Book and authentic Calendar of Contemporary Saints, 1975; "Brother Ben" (Spock) is on Fri 2 May (Box 554)
  - Artwork
    - About Spock, three cartoons; 3 items (Oversize 1)
    - By Spock, 1976; poem to Mary Morgan by Spock, done in calligraphy and watercolor; 1 item (Oversize 3)
    - Of Spock, ink, watercolor, crayon, by various artists/creators; 5 items (Oversize 1)
    - To or for Spock, includes watercolor of marina and Spock's boat, signed and insccibed photo from painter and sculptor Alfred Duca; 3 items (Oversize 1)
    - To or for Spock, 1977; "The Owl and the Pussycat" poem done in calligraphy and watercolor by Gilbert Montalvo; name on the boat is "The Carapace"; 1 item (Oversize 3)
    - To or for Spock, 1966; 1972,; undated; untitled print by unidentified French artist, signed and inscribed to Ben (1966); "The Great Patriot" print by R. E. Souligny, signed and numbered, (circa 1972); untitled print by Minna Agins [?], signed; Dymaxion Sky-Ocean World, 2pp, signed and inscribed to Ben and Jane by Buckminster Fuller; 4 items (Map-case 60)
    - Miscellaneous, includes collage and pen-and-ink drawing by Dan Spock; several "Young Pioneer" style posters with text and signatures in Russian; signed Reagan cartoon by George Fisher; 10 items (Oversize 1)
  - Awards and honors
    - Ambulatory Pediatric Association, 1981 (Oversize 2)
    - American Academy of Child and Adolescent Psychiatry, 1987 (Box 490)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics, C. Anderson Aldrich Award, 1970 (Box 491)
    - American Civil Liberties Union of New Jersey, for leadership in the cause of liberty, 1971 (Box 492)
    - American Humanist Assocation, Humanist of the Year, 1968 (Box 491)
    - American Medical Association, 1986; membership certificate (Box 490)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, "The Common Sense Book of Why the Spocks Care", 1967 (Box 490)
    - Chicago Area Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, Jane Addams Peace Award, 1964 (Box 540)
    - City of New Orleans, Honorary Citizen, 1980 (Oversize 3)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons, 1967; certificate only, medallion not present in collection (Box 490)
    - Communications Art Magazine Award of Distinctive Merit, undated; photocopy only; award went to Doyle, Dane and Bernbach for their SANE ad in Saturday Review, for which Spock wrote the copy (Box 490)
    - Cuyahoga County Commissioners, for guest appearance at fundraiser, 1986 (Box 490)
    - Earth Environment University Roundtable / Earth Environment Academy of America, 1993 (Oversize 3)
    - First Unitarian Church of Los Angeles, Stephen H. Fritchman "Heretic" Award, 1986 (Box 492)
    - Frontier College, Fellow, 1972 (Oversize 3)
    - Isabella Geriatric Center, Hall of Fame Senior Citizen Award for Outstanding Achievement, undated (Box 492)
    - Jacksonville, Florida, Honorary Citizen, 1986 (Oversize 3)
    - Jeff and Karen Wattenmaker, First Official Karen-Jeff Award, 1967 (Box 490)
    - Massachusetts Senior Action Council, Lifetime of Activism Award, 1990 (Box 492)
    - Mayor's United Nations Committee, for contributions to world health, the welfare of children, and the adoption of the test ban treaty, 1964 (Box 491)
    - National Center for Infants, Toddlers and Families, Dolly Madison Award, 1996 (Oversize 3)
    - New York College of Podiatric Medicine, 1992 (Box 490)
    - New York College of Podiatric Medicine, honorary D.H.L., 1992 (Oversize 3)
    - New York Council for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 1968; 2 items, one honoring Benjamin and the other his wife Jane (Oversize 3)
    - Nanny Cay Marine Center, 1986; for a rowing race (Box 490)
    - National Committee for a SANE Nuclear Policy, 1963 (Box 490)
    - National Committee for a SANE Nuclear Policy, Eleanor Roosevelt Award, 1963 (Oversize 5)
    - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, Thomas Paine Award, 1968 (Box 492)
    - New York Society of Clinical Psychologists, Public Service Award, 1973; metal pieces are detached from wood base (Box 493)
    - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, Senior 65ers Award, 1966; two small laurel wreaths detached from base (Box 540)
    - SANE/Freeze Peace Award, 1987 (Oversize 5)
    - Sarasota, Florida, Honorary Citizen, 1984 (Box 490)
    - School Bell Award, 1958 (Box 490)
    - Society of Public Health Educators, 1965; large glass pyramid on wooden base (Box 540)
    - Society of Public Health Educators, citation, 1965; accopanied above award (Oversize 3)
    - Southern Colorado State College, for oustanding contributions to SCSC Student Symposium, 1971; metal piece detached from base (Box 493)
    - Syracuse University, recognition for support of Libraries, 1969; signed by Chancellor William Tolley (Box 490)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1965 (Box 491)
    - University of Durham, honorary Sc.D., 1962 (Box 490)
    - Wheelock College, honorary Ed.D., 1991 (Box 490)
    - World Summit for Children Candlelight Vigils, 1990 (Box 490)
    - Wright State University School of Medicine, 1977 (Oversize 3)
  - Bird list, 1998-1999 (Box 494)
  - Book schedules, 1985-1987; lists of books sent to Ben for feedback or comment (Box 494)
  - Bumper stickers and decals (Box 494)
  - Buttons, March on Washington, nuclear non-proliferation, peace movement, Nixon, grapes boycott, political candidates, etc.; some with attached notes or descriptions; 5 folders (Box 494)
  - Calendars, in many cases there are multiple calendars for a given year; includes pocket calendars, desk calendars, hanging calendars with photographs, homemade calendar sheets, etc.
    - Calendars, 1955-1958; 2 folders (Box 494)
    - Calendars, 1960-1962; 1967-1974; 8 folders (Box 495)
    - Calendars, 1975-1979; 6 folders (Box 496)
    - Calendars, 1980-1981; 6 folders (Box 497)
    - Calendars, 1981-1983; 5 folders (Box 498)
    - Calendars, 1983-1987; 8 folders (Box 499)
    - Calendars, 1988-1994; 1998,; 2004 (Box 500)
    - Hanging wall calendars, large, 1977; 1991,; 1992,; 1994,; 2005; 5 items (Oversize 4)
    - Hanging wall calendars, very large, 1986-1994; 6 items (Oversize 6)
  - Clippings, includes articles and letters about Spock, letters to the editor by Spock, articles about issues of interest to Spock (e.g. Viet Nam, peace movement)
    - Clippings, 1928; 1950-1966; 9 folders (Box 501)
    - Clippings, 1967-1968; 7 folders (Box 502)
    - Clippings, 1968; 6 folders (Box 503)
    - Clippings, 1968; 5 folders (Box 504)
    - Clippings, 1969; 5 folders (Box 505)
    - Clippings, 1969-1970; 7 folders (Box 506)
    - Clippings, 1970-1971; 7 folders (Box 507)
    - Clippings, 1971-1972; 6 folders (Box 508)
    - Clippings, 1972-1976; 9 folders (Box 509)
    - Clippings, 1977-1982; 8 folders (Box 510)
    - Clippings, 1983-1990; 9 folders (Box 511)
    - Clippings, 1991-1993; 7 folders (Box 512)
    - Clippings, 1994-1999; 2003,; undated; 10 folders (Box 513)
    - Clippings, 1987; oversize scrapbook (Oversize 14)
    - Whole issues, 1954; 1959,; 1965,; 1967-1969; 10 folders (Box 514)
    - Whole issues, oversize, 1967-1969 (Oversize 7)
    - Whole issues, 1970-1974; 1977,; 1979,; 1981-1982; 13 folders (Box 515)
    - Whole issues, oversize, 1970-1974 (Oversize 8)
    - Whole issues, 1983-1988; 1990; 10 folders (Box 516)
    - Whole issues, 1991-1992; 1995-1996,; 1998,; undated; 3 folders (Box 517)
  - Dreams, Ben (Box 518)
  - Dreams, Mary (Box 518)
  - Fabric items
    - Banner, small, black thunderbird in white circle on red ground, accompanying note in pencil reads "given to me by carnation pickers of Colorado, affiiliated with grape pickers" (Box 541)
    - Banners with circle of handprints and Spock's name, 1968; printed black on white; 2 items (Box 541)
    - Doctoral hood, Hartford University, honorary D.H.L., 1965; red and white (Box 541)
    - Doctoral hood, Yale University, honorary D.H.L., 1965; dark blue, embroidered with Spock's name in white inside the collar (Box 541)
    - Doctoral hood, unidentified, light blue (Box 541)
    - Embroidery piece, "Dr. Spock" with flower, signed Aron Oglesby (Box 541)
    - Marshal's sleeve band [?], 1969; white satin, printed with "Marshal" and peace signs, written in pencil on back "Mobilization, Washington D.C." (Box 541)
    - Potholders, crocheted, noted as "sent by Mrs. Clark"; 2 items (Box 541)
    - South Vietnam Women's Union for Liberation silk scarf (Box 541)
    - "Stop the Killing" black felt band (Box 541)
    - T-shirt, "Championnat du Monde Medaille d'Or", printed with photo of Ben and rowing crew (Box 541)
    - Unidentified small black item printed with gold design (Box 541)
  - Financial miscellany, 1927-1928; 1930-1933,; 1952-1960; budgets, expense lists, etc.; 3 folders (Box 518)
  - Interview schedules, 1986; 1988-1989; includes in-person and telephone (Box 518)
  - Japan trip, 1979 (Box 518)
  - "Joint session" notes (Box 518)
  - Journal [?], Mary Morgan (Box 518)
  - Love beads, 3 items (Box 518)
  - Maps
    - Cleveland, undated (Oversize 3)
    - Cleveland and Vicinity, undated (Oversize 3)
    - Garrett County [Maryland] Forest Areas, 1913 (Oversize 3)
    - Garrett County [Maryland] Topography and Election Districts, 1949 (Oversize 3)
    - [Garrett County, Maryland, Little Snaggy Mountains and Hoopoe Ridge area], undated (Oversize 3)
    - Northeastern Ohio, 1960 (Oversize 3)
    - Pymatuning Lake [Pennsylvania], very fragile, care should be taken when unfolding (Oversize 3)
  - Membership cards, assorted (Box 518)
  - Menus, daily (Box 518)
  - Newsletters / Christmas letters, Ben and Jane, 1951-1952; 1955-1962,; 1964-1967,; 1970,; undated (Box 518)
  - Newsletters / Christmas letters, Ben and Mary, 1997 (Box 518)
  - Peace Calendar, "Where am I Going?", 1975; introduction by Spock, published by War Resisters League (Box 554)
  - Photographs, family
    These early family photographs include Spock's parents and grandparents, and Ben as a child with his siblings.
    - Denny, Mr. and Mrs. (great great grandparents), undated (Box 519)
    - Europe, mostly France, 1925; pages from an album, many photos are coming loose (Oversize 10)
    - Hooper (great great grandmother), undated (Box 519)
    - Spock, Anne, undated (Box 519)
    - Spock, Benjamin Ives (father), undated; reproduction (Box 519)
    - Spock, Ben, 1904; 1907,; 1908,; 1924,; undated; some with mother Mildred; includes rowing, Yale; prints, negatives (Box 519)
    - Spock, Ben and Jane, 1927; undated; includes photo of them on their honeymoon (Box 519)
    - Spock, Betty, 1909; 1941,; undated (Box 519)
    - Spock, Bobby; some with mother Mildred, circa 1912-1913 (Box 519)
    - Spock, Bobby, undated (Oversize 10)
    - Spock, Hiddy, 1906; 1910,; undated (Box 519)
    - Spock, Sally; some with her father (Box 519)
    - Spock, Sally, undated (Oversize 10)
    - Spock, William (grandfather) and family (Box 519)
    - Spock children (Ben and siblings), group photos; some include mother Mildred (Box 519)
    - Spock children (Ben and siblings), pages from an album (Oversize 10)
    - Spock family photo album, undated (Oversize 11)
    - Spock family portrait (Ben, Jane, children, grandchildren), undated (Oversize 10)
    - Spock family publicity photos (Ben, Jane, Michael, John) (Box 519)
    - Stoughton, Ada (grandmother), 1885; undated; includes some with daughter Laura (Box 519)
    - Stoughton, Ada (grandmother), 1872; with daughter Laura (Oversize 10)
    - Stoughton, Mildred and siblings, 1892; undated (Box 519)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 519)
  - Photographs
    Dated photographs are arranged first, chronologically, followed by undated photograps arranged alphabetically. Wherever possible, descriptions of the photographs have been taken verbatim from handwritten information on the envelopes, or on the back of the photographs themselves. In many cases there are no prints, only negatives. Spelling of names may or may not be correct, and may vary from one occurrence to another.
    - Ben, Parents magazine, 1947; prints (Box 519)
    - Queens, NY, Ben giving talk, circa 1953; prints (Box 519)
    - Dr. Spock Show, 1955; prints (Box 519)
    - Buzzard Bay, MA, sailing with friends on the Turtle, 1958; prints (Box 519)
    - New York Times portraits, 1960; prints (Box 519)
    - University of Durham, Ben receiving honorary doctorate; Ben, Charlie Chaplin, others, 1962; prints (Box 519)
    - Ben, Michael, John, 1962; prints (Oversize 10)
    - Doctors meeting with John F. Kennedy regarding medical care for the aged, 1962 Mar 27; prints (Box 519)
    - Ben speaking for peace in Los Angeles; Ben, Steve Allen, Ava Helen Pauling, Linus Pauling, 1963 Apr 23; prints (Box 519)
    - Lake Erie College, OH, commencement address, 1963 Jun; prints (Box 519)
    - White House, 1963 Aug (Box 519)
    - SANE national convention; Ben, Seymour Melman, Stuart Hughes, 1964; prints (Box 519)
    - Ben, publicity photos; includes correspondence, 1965; prints (Oversize 10)
    - U.S. Public Health Service, Atlanta, GA, publicizing measles vaccine; Ben, Dr. James Goddard, 1965; prints (Box 519)
    - Ben receiving honorary doctorate, University of Hartford, 1965; prints (Box 519)
    - Wayne Morse, Madison Square Garden; Morse was first senator to support the peace movement, 1965 Jun 8; prints (Box 519)
    - National Dental Health Assembly; Ben, Jane, Cohen, 1966 Feb 6-8; prints (Box 519)
    - Ben, Martin Luther King, Jr. on Irv Kupcinet's show, 1967; prints (Box 519)
    - Anti-war parade, Chicago, IL; Ben and Martin Luther King, Jr. in front row of march, 1967 Mar 25; prints (Box 519)
    - Anti-Vietnam War Rally; Ben, Jane, Lord Brockway, other MPs, 1967 Jun; negatives (Box 519)
    - Lawrence Rosenblum; includes correspondence, 1967-1968; slides (Box 519)
    - Marcia Barrabee; includes correspondence, 1968; slides (Box 519)
    - Ben speaking at UCLA, 1968 Jan; prints (Box 519)
    - Hughes Hospital, CT; Ben, Jane, Mildred Spock; includes correspondence with nurse Lee Reidy, 1968 May; prints (Box 519)
    - Boston Globe; includes correspondence and clipping, 1969; prints (Box 519)
    - handwritten on back: "Discussing your feelings about the contempt charges", 1969; prints (Oversize 10)
    - Ben at unidentified event, 1969; mounted print (Oversize 10)
    - Mary Morgan, unidentified charity event?, 1970s; negatives (Box 519)
    - Virgin Islands, aboard Carapace; Jim and Kathy Maloney, 1970s; prints (Box 519)
    - North Vietnam, 1970 Jun; prints (Box 519)
    - Ben at Lake Superior State College, 1971; prints (Box 519)
    - Press conference, San Jose, 1972 Oct; prints (Box 519)
    - First Unitarian Church, San Jose, reception for Ben, 1973; prints (Box 519)
    - Greenwich Village, NY, Redbook talk, 1974 Oct; prints (Box 519)
    - Berkeley, CA, David Teller, Micky, late 1970s; prints (Box 520)
    - Ben, Mary Morgan and others, late 1970s; negatives (Box 520)
    - David Teller photos, Micky, Berkeley, CA, late 1970s; negatives (Box 520)
    - Robert Drye, 1975; prints (Box 520)
    - Madison Ave. Apt. NY, Mary and Ben, 1975 Dec; prints (Box 520)
    - Ben running for The People's Party, 1976 Feb; prints (Box 520)
    - Berkeley, CA, Andrea's birthday, 1976 Aug; prints (Box 520)
    - Salt Lake City, UT, Steve, Diana, Stewart, Stephanie, 1976 Aug; prints (Box 520)
    - Boston Globe, 1977 Feb; negatives (Box 520)
    - Ben's 74th birthday party, 1977 May 2; prints (Box 520)
    - Ukiah, CA, 1977 Jun; negatives (Box 520)
    - Moscow, 1977 Jul; negatives (Box 520)
    - Moscow, USSR, 1977 Jul; prints (Box 520)
    - Russia, 1977 Jul; negatives (Box 520)
    - Budapest, Hungary, beach, Helen, Ben, Maun?, 1977 Aug; negatives (Box 520)
    - Turtle, ME, 1977 Aug-Sep; negatives (Box 520)
    - Frog's birthday party, 1977 Sep; negatives (Box 520)
    - Hiddy, goats, 1977 Sep; negatives (Box 520)
    - House, birthday party, Leonard and Jean, 1977 Nov; negatives (Box 520)
    - BVI, Maine, Hogie, Dorca, David, 1978; negatives (Box 520)
    - Fayetteville, AR, Ginger, Marilyn, 7th grade, 1978; negatives (Box 520)
    - Parenting conference; includes correspondence, 1978; prints (Box 520)
    - New York, Ginger, 1978 Mar; negatives (Box 520)
    - Pubilcity photos, Arkansas, 1978 Mar; contact sheets (Box 520)
    - Zoo, Washington DC, Ginger, Smithsonian, 1978 Mar; negatives (Box 520)
    - BVI, Courtney, Ginger, 1978 May-Jun; negatives (Box 520)
    - Virgin Islands, 1978 Jun; negatives (Box 520)
    - Berkeley, CA, Hogie's birthday party, 1978 Jul; negatives (Box 520)
    - Maine, Mike ("Frog") and Judy Spock, 1978 Aug; negatives (Box 520)
    - Thanksgiving, birthday, 1978 Nov; negatives (Box 520)
    - Mom at Christmas, 1978 Dec; negatives (Box 520)
    - BVI, Hogie and David, 1979 Jan; negatives; 2 folders (Box 520)
    - London, 1979 Mar; negatives (Box 520)
    - Salt Lake City, UT, Sundance, Robert Redford, 1979 Mar 1-3; negatives (Box 520)
    - Test, Ben, [1979] Jun 19; prints, negatives (Box 520)
    - Camden, ME, [1979] Jun 20; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Irene, 1979 Jun 20; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Monhegan Island, ME, [1979] Jun 21; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - BVI, Europe, Maine, Japan, 1979 [Jul]; negatives (Box 521)
    - New York, 1979 Jul; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Paris, France, 1979 Jul; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Salzburg and Germany, [1979 Jul]; negatives (Box 521)
    - Venice, Italy, 1979 Jul; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Vienna, Germany, eagle's nest, 1979 Jul; negatives (Box 521)
    - Japan, 1979 Jul- Aug; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Boston, MA, Denver, CO., 1979 Jul 1, 2; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Frenchboro, ME, 1979 Aug; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Hiddy, 1979 Aug; negatives (Box 521)
    - Rogers, AR, homecoming parade, 1979 Nov; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Esculapia Hollow, AR, homecoming, birthday, 1979 Nov 27; negatives (Box 521)
    - Ben, miscellaneous, 1979-1981; prints (Box 521)
    - Ben, Mary Morgan, others; Ben in classroom, [1980s]; prints, negatives (Box 521)
    - Bentonville, AR, homecoming parade, [1980s]; negatives (Box 521)
    - Leaving San Juan; Chip, Lorraine, Mac, Karen, [1980s]; prints (Box 521)
    - Ben, Mary Morgan, 1980 Jan; prints (Box 521)
    - BVI, Johnny, Ginger, Erin, 1980 Jan; negatives (Box 521)
    - Virgin Gorda, BVI, Mike Kilbride, Erin, 1980 Feb; negatives (Box 521)
    - BVI, Adrea [Andrea], Jim, Daffney [Daphne], Ben, 1980 Feb; negatives (Box 521)
    - BVI, Betty Brooker, 1980 Feb; negatives (Box 521)